// const questionList = [
// 	[
// 		{questionSetId: 1,questionId: 415451, question: '1+1=?', answer: '2', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 1,questionId: 435626, question: '1+2=?', answer: '3', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 1,questionId: 254325, question: '1+3=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 1,questionId: 346543, question: '2+3=?', answer: '5', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '5',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 	],
// 	[
// 		{questionSetId: 2,questionId: 543737, question: '4-2=?', answer: '2', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 2,questionId: 547643, question: '4-1=?', answer: '3', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 2,questionId: 573556, question: '2+2=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 2,questionId: 537577, question: '6-2=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '5',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 	],
// 	[
// 		{questionSetId: 3,questionId: 426266, question: '2+0=?', answer: '2', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 3,questionId: 536564, question: '1+2=?', answer: '3', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 3,questionId: 565467, question: '8-4=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 		{questionSetId: 3,questionId: 562563, question: '1+4=?', answer: '5', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '5',option4: '4', score: 100},
// 	]
// ]

const questionList = [
		{questionSetId: 1, question: '1+1=?', answer: '2', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 1, question: '1+2=?', answer: '3', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 1, question: '1+3=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 1, question: '2+3=?', answer: '5', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '5',option4: '4', score: 100},
	
		{questionSetId: 2, question: '4-2=?', answer: '2', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 2, question: '4-1=?', answer: '3', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 2, question: '2+2=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 2, question: '6-2=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '5',option4: '4', score: 100},
	
		{questionSetId: 3, question: '2+0=?', answer: '2', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 3, question: '1+2=?', answer: '3', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 3, question: '8-4=?', answer: '4', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '3',option4: '4', score: 100},
		{questionSetId: 3, question: '1+4=?', answer: '5', option1: '1',option2: '2',option3: '5',option4: '4', score: 100},
	]

module.exports = {
	questionList
}